<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<!--
	Artefacts (active)
-->

<string_table>
	<string id="st_af_itcher_name">
		<text>"Itcher"</text>
	</string>  
	<string id="st_af_itcher_descr">
		<text>A formation of thermal nature, consisting of two separated layers. Surface is a hard, dense metamorphic rock with deep scars covering the entire body and the soft, yellow core is formed from an unknown organic nature. Actively consumes heat and remains cool at all times.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]RADIOACTIVE EMISSIONS:\n
		%c[d_blue] • beta particles\n
		</text>
	</string> 

	<string id="st_af_pin_name">
		<text>"Pin"</text>
	</string>  
	<string id="st_af_pin_descr">
		<text>A small artefact formed by thermal anomalies in the Zone under extreme temperatures. Looks suggest that it was once an organ of a vascular plant. Further studies show that other organic tissues are fused deep inside. The stem doesn't hold any useful properties. The small pins found on the artefact reduce the temperature of the user's body and cool all objects in their vicinity.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]RADIOACTIVE EMISSIONS:\n
		%c[d_blue] • beta particles\n
		%c[d_green] • gamma rays\n
		</text>
	</string>  
	
	<string id="st_af_cristall_name">
		<text>"Crystal"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_cristall_descr">
		<text>This artefact is formed in anomalous zones with intense thermal activity. Actively consumes heat and remains cool at all times. Its inner core is not radioactive and considered to be of exceptional beauty if polished and refined. Only the first 1cm of its outer layer emits radiation.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]RADIOACTIVE EMISSIONS:\n
		%c[d_blue] • beta particles\n
		%c[d_green] • gamma rays\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_fireball_name">
		<text>"Fireball"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fireball_descr">
		<text>A spherical artefact made of a red-coloured crystal, created in the Burner anomaly. Has a constant temperature of 24 degrees Celsius, regardless of its surroundings.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]RADIOACTIVE EMISSIONS:\n
		%c[d_blue] • beta particles\n
		%c[d_green] • gamma rays\n
		%c[d_orange] • neutrons\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_blood_name">
		<text>"Stone Blood"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_blood_descr">
		<text>A reddish formation of compressed fossilized plants, soil and animal debris.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]RADIOACTIVE EMISSIONS:\n
		%c[d_blue] • beta particles\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_mincer_meat_name">
		<text>"Meat Chunk"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_mincer_meat_descr">
		<text>This artefact has a soft, porous, skin-like texture. Resembles and acts like a sponge.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]RADIOACTIVE EMISSIONS:\n
		%c[d_blue] • beta particles\n
		%c[d_green] • gamma rays\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_bracelet_name">
		<text>"Bracelet"</text>
	</string>  
	<string id="st_af_bracelet_descr">
		<text>Formed from a common species of bryophyte plant under high exposure to radioactive and chemical anomalies. Alters the pH of liquids in comes in contact with to that of water (7pH).\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]RADIOACTIVE EMISSIONS:\n
		%c[d_blue] • beta particles\n
		%c[d_green] • gamma rays\n
		</text>
	</string>  
	
	<string id="st_af_baloon_name">
		<text>"Bubble"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_baloon_descr">
		<text>A compound of several hollow organic formations. Emits a gaseous substance. Has a stable temperature regardless of its surroundings.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]RADIOACTIVE EMISSIONS:\n
		%c[d_blue] • beta particles\n
		%c[d_green] • gamma rays\n
		%c[d_orange] • neutrons\n 
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_electra_sparkler_name">
		<text>"Sparkler"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_electra_sparkler_descr">
		<text>This artefact has the appearance of translucent spider webs and is sticky with properties of glue. Can be found most commonly in or near electro anomalies.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]RADIOACTIVE EMISSIONS:\n
		%c[d_blue] • beta particles\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_sponge_name">
		<text>"Sponge"</text>
	</string>  
	<string id="st_af_sponge_descr">
		<text>Ecologists believe it to be an advanced lifeform with self-awareness inherited from living creatures. Oddly moves on its own.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]RADIOACTIVE EMISSIONS:\n
		%c[d_blue] • beta particles\n
		%c[d_green] • gamma rays\n
		</text>
	</string> 
	
	<string id="st_af_ring_name">
		<text>"Ring"</text>
	</string>  
	<string id="st_af_ring_descr">
		<text>A very small artefact of electric nature. Difficult to spot. Consists of two ring-shaped materials of organic nature. Defies the first law of thermodynamics as it never stops spinning. Scientists suggest that this artefact inherits gravitational properties from Vortex anomalies.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]RADIOACTIVE EMISSIONS:\n
		%c[d_blue] • beta particles\n
		%c[d_green] • gamma rays\n
		</text>
	</string> 
	
	<string id="st_af_electra_flash_name">
		<text>"Flash"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_electra_flash_descr">
		<text>This artefact is very similar in appearance to "Moonlight" and resembles a plasma globe.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]RADIOACTIVE EMISSIONS:\n
		%c[d_blue] • beta particles\n
		%c[d_green] • gamma rays\n
		%c[d_orange] • neutrons\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_cristall_flower_name">
		<text>"Stone Flower"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_cristall_flower_descr">
		<text>Resembles melted cheese interspersed with sapphire-like stones. Only the yellow outer shell of the artefact appears to give off radiation. It is possible to extract the non-radioactive blue parts for jewellery and other industrial purposes as, if cleaned properly and polished, they look strikingly like sapphires.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]RADIOACTIVE EMISSIONS:\n
		%c[d_blue] • beta particles\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_lobster_eyes_name">
		<text>"Lobster Eyes"</text>
	</string>  
	<string id="st_af_lobster_eyes_descr">
		<text>Has the shape of two eyes fused together with the outer surface being very thick.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]RADIOACTIVE EMISSIONS:\n
		%c[d_blue] • beta particles\n
		%c[d_green] • gamma rays\n
		</text>
	</string> 
	
	<string id="st_af_electra_moonlight_name">
		<text>"Moonlight"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_electra_moonlight_descr">
		<text>This unique electrostatic artefact resonates under the influence of psy-waves.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]RADIOACTIVE EMISSIONS:\n
		%c[d_blue] • beta particles\n
		%c[d_green] • gamma rays\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_black_spray_name">
		<text>"Black Spray"</text>
	</string>  
	<string id="st_af_black_spray_descr">
		<text>A rare artefact. Little is known about its properties and origins. Shares a similar shape to other sapphire-like artefacts. The organic nature of the stem suggests that it formed from vascular plants under exposure to dangerous psy-fields and electromagnetic waves.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]RADIOACTIVE EMISSIONS:\n
		%c[d_blue] • beta particles\n
		%c[d_green] • gamma rays\n
		%c[d_orange] • neutrons\n
		</text>
	</string>  
	
	<string id="st_af_medusa_name">
		<text>"Jellyfish"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_medusa_descr">
		<text>Very common in the Zone. Gravitational artefact able to shield the body and objects from physical impacts.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]RADIOACTIVE EMISSIONS:\n
		%c[d_blue] • beta particles\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_vyvert_name">
		<text>"Wrenched"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_vyvert_descr">
		<text>Appears in places with increased gravitational activity. Although it seems almost organic, it is actually more similar to coral.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]RADIOACTIVE EMISSIONS:\n
		%c[d_blue] • beta particles\n
		%c[d_green] • gamma rays\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_empty_name">
		<text>"Empty"</text>
	</string>  
	<string id="st_af_empty_descr">
		<text>Two disks of organic formation (commonly lipids, cellulose and lignin) with nothing but empty space in between. A unique gravitational field exists in the centre that stabilizes the distance between the disks. Any attempt to press the disks together, or pull them apart will fail due to rapid positive/negative changes in the gravitational field.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]RADIOACTIVE EMISSIONS:\n
		%c[d_blue] • beta particles\n
		%c[d_green] • gamma rays\n
		</text>
	</string> 
 	
	<string id="st_af_full_empty_name">
		<text>"Full Empty"</text>
	</string>  
	<string id="st_af_full_empty_descr">
		<text>Similar to Empty, this artefact consist of two disks of organic formation connected by a unique gravitational field in between. The gravitational field generated releases photons of light referred to as the "galaxy effect" by scientists. Some claim that "Full Empty" is capable of stopping 9mm bullets fired at point blank though this has not been tested. Incredibly dense.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]RADIOACTIVE EMISSIONS:\n
		%c[d_blue] • beta particles\n
		%c[d_green] • gamma rays\n
		%c[d_orange] • neutrons\n
		</text>
	</string> 
	
	<string id="st_af_night_star_name">
		<text>"Nightstar"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_night_star_descr">
		<text>A glowing artefact that can generate a locally directed low-gravity field. Widely used by stalkers along with Gravi, a similar artefact, to increase maximum carry load. Only the outter core emits any radiation. "Nightstart" is highly sought after by jewelers due to its beautiful inner core, though unskilled treatment can cause the artefact to explode with power sufficient to level a small building.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]RADIOACTIVE EMISSIONS:\n
		%c[d_blue] • beta particles\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_gravi_name">
		<text>"Gravi"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_gravi_descr">
		<text>Formed from metallic substances exposed to prolonged gravitation. Capable of sustaining a powerful anti-gravitational field, reducing the weight of all objects in proximity.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]RADIOACTIVE EMISSIONS:\n
		%c[d_blue] • beta particles\n
		%c[d_green] • gamma rays\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_gold_fish_name">
		<text>"Goldfish"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_gold_fish_descr">
		<text>Direct successor to, and a superior version of, the Gravi artefact. Produced in an extremely rare phenomenon where three Gravi artefacts interact and combine singularity fields. Highly valuable. Creates a constant anti-gravitational singularity field, reducing the weight of all objects in its proximity. Sometimes, the velocity of moving objects inside its radius will rapidly increase up to dangerous levels. Some stalkers have even been known to disappear for no apparent reason, leaving only a "Goldfish" behind.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]RADIOACTIVE EMISSIONS:\n
		%c[d_blue] • beta particles\n
		%c[d_green] • gamma rays\n
		%c[d_orange] • neutrons\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_dummy_glassbeads_name">
		<text>"Mama's Beads"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dummy_glassbeads_descr">
		<text>Created in the Burner anomaly, the artefact is shaped like a DNA helix. The artefact constantly pulsates, increase the metabolism of any living creature and accelerating coagulation and the healing of wounds, though the mechanism behind the effects of this artefact are unknown.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]RADIOACTIVE EMISSIONS:\n
		%c[d_blue] • beta particles\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_eye_name">
		<text>"Eye"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_eye_descr">
		<text>Often generated around heat anomalies, this artefact resembles that of a human eye.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]RADIOACTIVE EMISSIONS:\n
		%c[d_blue] • beta particles\n
		%c[d_green] • gamma rays\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_fire_name">
		<text>"Flame"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fire_descr">
		<text>Forms in areas of high thermal activity. Produces powerful infrared emissions which intensify metabolic processes, healing wounds incredibly quick. Has gained a reputation as a "life saver" between many stalkers.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]RADIOACTIVE EMISSIONS:\n
		%c[d_blue] • beta particles\n
		%c[d_green] • gamma rays\n
		%c[d_orange] • neutrons\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_dummy_battery_name">
		<text>"Battery"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dummy_battery_descr">
		<text>Quite popular in the Zone and valued by its residents and visitors alike for its energizing properties.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]RADIOACTIVE EMISSIONS:\n
		%c[d_blue] • beta particles\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_dummy_dummy_name">
		<text>"Shell"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dummy_dummy_descr">
		<text>Composed of two disks of bluish colour connected by a semitransparent material of unknown nature. Considered devoid of any useful properties by many scientists for a long time.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]RADIOACTIVE EMISSIONS:\n
		%c[d_blue] • beta particles\n
		%c[d_green] • gamma rays\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_ice_name">
		<text>"Snowflake"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ice_descr">
		<text>Also colloquially known as "Radioactive Snowflake". Significantly increases the wearers muscle tone, greatly improving stamina recovery. Due to its high radioactivity, stalkers in possession of it are sometimes jokingly referred to as "Radioactive Snowflakes".\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]RADIOACTIVE EMISSIONS:\n
		%c[d_blue] • beta particles\n
		%c[d_green] • gamma rays\n
		%c[d_orange] • neutrons\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_soul_name">
		<text>"Soul"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_soul_descr">
		<text>A unique organic artefact that secretes a slimy goo that dramatically increases the recovery rate of wounds. Considered a valuable collector's item.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]RADIOACTIVE EMISSIONS:\n
		%c[d_blue] • beta particles\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_fuzz_kolobok_name">
		<text>"Kolobok"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fuzz_kolobok_descr">
		<text>A relatively rare artefact formed in chemical areas. Highly valued for its ability to heal most kinds of wounds and stop bleeding in a matter of minutes, though needles of the artefact also cause small but quick-healing wounds which bring discomfort, itching and reduced stamina.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]RADIOACTIVE EMISSIONS:\n
		%c[d_blue] • beta particles\n
		%c[d_green] • gamma rays\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_glass_name">
		<text>"Firefly"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_glass_descr">
		<text>Interacts with fields unknown to science, considerably speeding up the regeneration of tissue and organs in living organisms, as well as normalizing metabolic processes. Can get a badly wounded stalker back on his feet in a matter of minutes though some report not being able to walk for hours after use.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]RADIOACTIVE EMISSIONS:\n
		%c[d_blue] • beta particles\n
		%c[d_green] • gamma rays\n
		%c[d_orange] • neutrons\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_compass_name">
		<text>"Compass"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_compass_descr">
		<text>An incredibly rare artefact. It is believed that it can help traverse the most complex anomaly fields completely unharmed, though very few know how to handle it properly. Can interact with moving objects, causing some to completely disappear or perhaps teleport.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]RADIOACTIVE EMISSIONS:\n
		%c[d_blue] • beta particles\n
		%c[d_green] • gamma rays\n
		%c[d_orange] • neutrons\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_oasis_heart_name">
		<text>"Heart of the Oasis"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_oasis_heart_descr">
		<text>Found at the centre of the legendary Oasis. The Heart is a crystallized plant which has acquired the healing properties of the Oasis.  A true miracle. Very sensitive to outer sources of energy and its surrounding environment.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]RADIOACTIVE EMISSIONS:\n
		%c[d_blue] • beta particles\n
		%c[d_green] • gamma rays\n
		%c[d_orange] • neutrons\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_death_lamp_name">
		<text>"Death Lamp"</text>
	</string>  
	<string id="st_af_death_lamp_descr">
		<text>"Big, red and cursed", is how the locals prefer to describe the Death Lamp and often referred to as the "Seed of Satan". Many traders believe the rumours surrounding the artefact, thus refusing to buy it and little is known about its origins. First discovered a few years ago by a group of three experienced stalkers, shortly after delivering the artefact to the Ecologists in Yantar, two of them were found dead with a horrific expression on their face, though nothing is known about the fate of the third stalker. Following the accident, members of the science team who studied the artefact had reported having nightmare disorder in the days to follow.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]RADIOACTIVE EMISSIONS:\n
		%c[d_blue] • beta particles\n
		%c[d_green] • gamma rays\n
		%c[d_orange] • neutrons\n 
		%c[d_red] • positrons\n
		</text>
	</string> 
	
	<string id="st_af_monolith_name">
		<text>"Volat Emerald"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_monolith_descr">
		<text>The origins of artefacts such as this one are a mystery, as they are rarely found outside the northernmost parts of the Zone. Grants the wearer a notable level of protection against most of the Zone's environmental hazards. One of the few active artefacts that can be safely handled without lead containers. When you hold it your flesh feels dry and flaky, your bones hard and stiff, the ligaments in your joints squeaky and brittle. Thick armor or great supernatural vitality would be needed by anyone intending to wear this artefact into battle.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_black_name">
		<text>"Black Stone"</text>
  </string>
  <string id="st_af_black_descr">
		<text>At first seems to protect its user but instead, slowly kills them. Some stalkers suspect the artefact is a shard of the Monolith.
		</text>
  </string>
	
	<!-- MLR -->
	<string id="st_af_misery_bread_name">
		<text>"Anomalous Bread"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_misery_bread_descr">
		<text>A piece of bread as dark as the soul of the person that left it. Definitely not safe to eat.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]RADIOACTIVE EMISSIONS:\n
		%c[d_blue] • beta particles\n
		%c[d_green] • gamma rays\n
		%c[d_orange] • neutrons\n 
		%c[d_red] • positrons\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<!-- NEW -->
	<string id="st_af_quest_b14_twisted">
		 <text>"Twisted Wheel"</text>
  </string>
  <string id="st_af_quest_b14_twisted_descr">
		<text>This was once the dredge station wheel. It is now a radioactive, half-converted twisted artifact. No notable properties.
		</text>
  </string>

</string_table>